# **LES QUINES**

403-392-9251 les.quines@gmail.com

Innisfail, AB Canada

#### **PROFILE**

I am a mature individual with a diverse set of work experience in making things work and I have a passion for learning. I was a Canadian air force aircraft technician.

I switched to the world of computers and the internet wanting to know how they work. I am enjoying learning web technologies and creating functional websites and apps in the process. I get great satisfaction in finding solutions to problems. I was a QA Test Analyst for Ceridian and Westjet.

Highly motivated to succeed, I am a self-taught web developer with valuable skills and I am highly motivated to learn new skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Semi-Retired — 2008 - Present

Travelled extensively and built a house. In my spare time, I devoted myself to learning and absorbing all I could about the creative aspects of programming. With focus on web development through self-study of online courses and the internet.

## QA Test Analyst, Westjet, Calgary — 2006-2008

Carried out manual and automated testing on the airline's booking site.

#### QA Test Analyst, Ceridian, Winnipeg, MB and Calgary, AB — 2001-2006

Testing the company's HR/Payroll Insync software. Carried out manual and automated testing using Rational Test.

#### IT Admin, Canadian Forces, Winnipeg, MB — 2000-2001

IT LAN administration duties for 407 squadron, controlling user access to network and installing software and hardware. In addition as administrator for the squadron's Aircraft Maintenance Management Information System(AMMIS), carrying out backups, updates and patches.

#### Aircraft Technician, Canadian Forces — 1980-2000

Service, maintain, inspect and repair various military aircrafts. Assisted in flight safety investigations.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Udemy Online Courses**

- Web Development Bootcamp 2020
- React
- Wordpress
- iOS Apps

# **Red River College, Winnipeg, MB**

• Computer Analyst/Programmer — 1998-2000

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Git

## **WORKING ON THESE SKILLS**

Mongo, Express, EJS, Node, NPM, React, Vue, Bootstrap, JQuery, REST API, JSON, PHP, Wordpress

#### **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.